...there was no way he could've come up
with this whole experiment thing.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me. Little idea?
Yeah, he tried to explain it to me.
I didn't really understand it...
(Sheldon:)Of course you didn't.
He said "little idea"?
Oh. Well, no.
I mean, not in those words...
In what words, then, exactly?
The exact words aren't really...
(Penny:)- It's more the spirit in which...
- What did he say?
(Penny:)You had a lucky hunch.
(Leonard(coming out of apartment):)I've been thinking.
Instead of arguing about this, why...?
(Sheldon:)Don't you ever speak to me again.
(Penny:)What...?
Oh, he:
(Leonard:)Okay, I'm leaving for the conference.
- Have fun presenting my "lucky hunch."
- Sheldon, I didn't mean it like that.
- Why did you say it?
- I don't know...